const quiz1data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "I _____ Karen since 1994.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "have known", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "knew", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present perfect when we want to talk about unfinished actions or states or habits that started in the past and continue to the present. Usually we use it to say "how long" and we need "since" or "for". We often use stative verbs.'
   },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "How long have you ___, Mr Smith?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "been waiting", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "waited", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We normally  use the present perfect continuous to emphasize about the duration of an activity.'
   },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Your voice sounds strange. Have you ___?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "been drinking", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "drunk", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Duration and/or repetition.'
   },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Kelly has ___ to call her husband all morning.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "tried", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "been trying", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Repetition (all morning)'
   },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Sam ____ here for seven months.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "has worked", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "has been working", isCorrect: false },
        {answer: 'both', isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: "Sometimes there's really no difference in meaning between the present perfect and the present perfect continuous. This is especially the case with verbs such as 'live','work', and 'study'."
   },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Have you ___ the book yet?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "read", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "been reading", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'yet' and 'already' with the present perfect  simple."
   },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What have you ___ to your hair? It looks awful!",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "done", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "been doing", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present perfect to talk about something that happened in the recent past (a finished action), and we can see the result in the present (focus on result).'
   },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Sylvia ___ Tom for the past four months.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "has dated", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "has been dating", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present perfect continuous to talk about repeated activities which started at a particular time in the past and are still continuing up until now.'
   },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "I have ___ Tokyo three times.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "visited", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "been visiting", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the present perfect to talk about a life experience. This experience happened sometime during a person's life. No matter when the experience happened."
   },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "I've ___ Janet for two years.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "been knowning", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "known", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use the present perfect to talk about unfinished actions that started in the past and are still true in the present. It's often used with stative verbs."
   },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "I've ___ my mom that all day.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "been telling", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "told", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Repetition (all day)'
   },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "He's ___ here for ten years.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "lived", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "been living", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use the present perfect continuous to talk about unfinished actions that started in the past and are still true in the present. We don't use the present perfect continuous with stative verbs."
   }
  ]
export default quiz1data
